https://www.wecarepds.com/terms-privacy/

Facebook-f
Instagram
Home
Who We Are
Who is WeCare?
Respite Care
Why Choose WeCare?
Who We Are
Who is WeCare?
Respite Care
Why Choose WeCare?
Privacy Policy
Our Commitment To PrivacyYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.The Information We CollectThis notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the website. On some pages, you can make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:NameAddressEmail addressPhone numberThe Way We Use InformationWe use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that request for information. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that process.We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.You can register with our website if you would like to receive our newsletter as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the applicable registration form.We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.Our Commitment To Data SecurityTo prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.How You Can Access Or Correct Your InformationYou can inquire about all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
Exceptional Care IsA Call Away
We’re sure that you have many questions and we are here to help 24 hours a day, 7 days a week. WeCare is committed to helping your family understand and benefit from our many service options.
CONTACT US TODAY
1852 Reisterstown RoadSuite 209Pikesville, MD 21208Phone: 410-602-3993Fax: 410-602-6277
Quick Links
Who We Are
What We Offer
Why Choose WeCare?
Why Choose WeCare?
Licensed as a Residential Service Agency by the Maryland Department of Health, Office of Healthcare Quality. Independently Owned and Operated.
©2020 WeCare Private Duty Services, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
Website by Marstudio
